Pei Song.
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
I'm okay.
Shiya.
Watch out!
Pei Ning.
Xiaoning.
Calm down.
Don't do anything stupid.
Turn back now.
There's still time.
Turn back.
Do you hear what you're saying?
Turn back
to continue being your lackey?
In your dreams.
My AI system
will soon be revealed to the public.
When that time comes,
I will completely replace you.
Pei Song
will forever be a thing of the past.
Xiaoning.
This is between you and me.
It has nothing to do with Shiya.
Let her go.
I'm the one you hate.
He said
it has nothing to do with you.
Pei Ning.
Don't move.
Stay here and be a good boy.
Otherwise,
I'll make sure you
never
see Song Shiya again.
I planted a
special signal band in your phone.
It's a 520 binary code.
When you are in danger,
just turn it on,
and I'll be able to find you.
Hello.
Jingyan.
Notify the police immediately
to track Shiya's location.
I sent you Shiya's signal frequency band.
Pei Ning took Shiya away.
Okay.
Keep yourself safe.
Shiya.
Pei Song.
Don't move.
It will explode.
That's my brother.
You found her so fast.
Wait a minute.
I'll show you something fun.
This countdown program
was carefully prepared by me.
This program
is in this computer.
If you crack it fast enough,
Song Shiya
won't die.
Otherwise...
Pei Song,
there's no time.
Leave me alone.
Pei Ning has already started uploading the program.
His algorithm still has loopholes.
If criminals exploit it,
and we don't stop him in time,
the consequences will be unimaginable.
Pei Song,
Pei Ning is stalling for time.
If Pei Ning is using my algorithm,
I'll see if I can remotely plant a Trojan
to destroy the program.
Hello?
Jingyan,
contact the police to track this IP
and find the server address.
It won't work.
16 digits.
If there's no character limit,
there are hundreds of millions of combinations.
The algorithm takes time to calculate.
We won't make it in time.
Brother, what is this?
I saw you liked math,
so I bought this for you.
You need to fill in the 81 blank squares
with numbers from 1 to 9,
and satisfy the horizontal and vertical lines.
The sum of the diagonals is the same.
Isn't this for kids?
It's not that simple.
Try it if you don't believe me.
Play with me.
Okay.
Come on.
Then let's do it one by one,
or what?
Look.
One, three, seven, two, six, nine.
So what is it?
489.
Let me try.